what's up my bodybuilding friends this
is Nick at bobbend.com and today we are
talking about the best supplements for
bodybuilding what we're talking about
here is supplements that can help with
muscle gain and fat loss and also
recovery as well so we got a whole range
of different supplements here today in
just about every category of supplement
you could ask for we've got protein
powders pre-workouts we've got sleep
aids creatine and a lot more so stick
around we're going to make you an expert
so you know which supplements are going
to be right for you I'm not a doctor and
this is a disclaimer to say this is not
medical advice and I'm not trying to be
a medical professional here before you
start any new supplement regimen or
nutrition regimen or uh exercise regime
in any kind of regimen if you're making
just about any changes to the way that
you conduct yourself with regards to
your health go to see a doctor to give
you some advice that can be
individualized based on your you know
medical history medications you take and
just the individual person that you are
with that said I'm just going to do you
a favor and let you know the number one
pick is on this list for supplements for
body building because you never expected
time you're busy passing really to get
to the gym is this one right here huge
supplements wreck is a pre-workout and
the thing is of all the supplements out
there provided and assuming your
calories and macronutrients are in check
the main thing is going to help you
build a muscle is not going to be
something that might potentially help
with the vasodilation or something it's
whatever helps you to get a bit more
work done in the gym now to be fair
those vasodilation supplements can help
but my point is what matters the most
outside of your regular diet is whatever
can help you to do more work in the gym
so what we have here is a very effective
pre-workout that's very strongly dosed
with a wide variety of ingredients so
there's stuff for naturally there's
caffeine quite a lot of it but it slow
release caffeine so some of it will come
on at the beginning of the workout some
will start to uh come on a little bit
later on so it's meant to have like less
of a giant spike in Crash than some
other products out there that's due to
the dye caffeine malate you've also get
other ingredients here like all the best
ones like beta in anhydrous for some
extra power output potentially According
to some research better alien for
endurance essentially for blood flow and
nitric oxide production and so on so we
think a solid pre-workout with a wide
range of non-caffeine ingredients is
your best bet to be the best supplement
for bodybuilder so that's a little hint
of what's to come in this video for now
let's have a really short little aside
about what to consider before buying
supplements for bodybuilding
the first thing is like assuming that
you're a competitive bodybuilder and you
don't have to be to engage in
bodybuilding because it's quite a
healthful activity in general to uh
focus on hypertrophy for a little bit
helps keep the joints happy that kind of
stuff but if you're if you're going to a
competition when you're thinking about
buying supplements consider how close
competition you are so as an easy
example here uh sometimes people cut
creatine out in the weeks before a
competition not always but sometimes the
creatine might not be the best pick at
that point uh if you are looking at fat
burners those are typically a better
pick in the last remaining weeks as
you're closing into a competition
whereas if you're a few months away then
you know you're likely going to be more
interested in gaining a bit of mask to
cut away the fat litter on so fat
burners might be more interesting in the
last few weeks a creatine might have
been dropped at that point also in the
last few weeks of competition people
sometimes tend to have trouble sleeping
occasionally because they're really low
on calories and typically doing a lot of
exercise that the body would rather you
have more calories for let's be honest
so like a sleep aid which might not be
quite necessary at the beginning of prep
when they tend to be eating a lot more
and and it's not quite as all-consuming
an Endeavor as things can get in those
last few weeks when you're sort of like
redlining it you know what I mean so
we've got to sleep supplement here we've
got creatine for the time is right a
pre-workout protein powder and a whole
lot more supplements but let's Circle
back to the number one pick which again
is wrecked here so there is no shortage
of pre-workouts out there that they'll
find an ingredient that sounds promising
and has interesting research supporting
it but they don't include the the
appropriate dosage so citrulline is a
really good example here so an amino
acids found in watermelon it's pretty
interesting with regard to potentially
increasing blood flow helping
vasodilation in that regard helping the
vascularity and also there's generally
Muscle Recovery as well getting more
blood and oxygen to the muscle uh the
effective dose though is a good five
grams and there's a lot of pre-workers
out there they'll say check it out we
have citrulline you've heard about that
right here's some stitching it'll be
like one gram so it's wise to not just
know what ingredients to look for but
also the dosages to look for wrecked
here has a very considerable eight grams
of citrulline per serving you can tell
it on their research and they're really
dug the rice and crust in their tears
and they're the same approach to all the
other ingredients here as well right so
the most popular pre-workout ingredients
if you didn't know this and there's the
caffeine citrulline bit of alanine and
Betadine anhydrous we talked about the
citrulline the beta en anhydrous that
has some interesting links to power
output they've done studies on bench
press and squat in particular and found
some positive results there it comes
from beets in nature and some greens too
then there's a beta alanine which is a
non-essential amino acid that has been
seen to help with endurance especially
strength endurance in that 10 to 20 rep
Mark and when you're focused on a
hypertrophy a lot of the time I thought
most of the time the Reps tend to be in
the higher end so beta only can be
really useful in that regard and also to
help them with cardio as well and
especially in like one to three minute
power output end which sounds a lot to
me like high intensity in full training
which many bodybuilders prefer as a
means for shredding some extra fat so
the ingredients here are very well dosed
all in line with the research which is
like you know two and a half to three
grams baiting anhydrous at least 1.6
grams of beta alanine this exceeds all
of those doses that are normally seen in
research there's also some other stuff
here though as well I'm not gonna go
through every single ingredient here
we've got a full article in our site for
that I'm coaching to check out in the
description below but just to really
quickly touch on they've got some
adaptogens here which are an interesting
area of supplementation and that they
can potentially help the body to manage
stress stress from a difficult workout
stress from having to count your
calories all day every day especially my
hard day the office this kind of stuff
so there's some lines made Mushroom in
here that might help with that and a lot
of bodybuilders these days they find
that supplementing with adaptogens
especially the close to competition day
can be really helpful right so you've
got all like the classic pre-workout
ingredients in this product but also a
lot of more interesting more novel ones
that aren't quite as common in
pre-workers they all come together here
the main thing though this is 350
milligrams of caffeine so that might be
a lot for some folks but as I mentioned
earlier number one 100 milligrams of
that is slow release so it'll con a
little bit later and number two the
ingredients here are so effectively
dosed you could have a little more than
half of a scoop you'll still get
effective doses of all the ingredients
and you'll get less caffeine so that's
the strategy you can consider taking as
well in any case the best pre-workout
for bodybuilding in our opinion is erect
from huge supplements next up the best
pre-workout without caffeine because you
can get sick of caffeine the other thing
is with fat burner supplements which a
lot of people take uh especially clothes
on a competition day most fat burners
have a considerable amount of caffeine
as well so there are a lot of folks that
don't want to have to be taking extra
caffeine on top of that in their
pre-workout there's no shortage of
caffeine free pre-workouts out there in
the market though for a variety of
reasons our favorite one is right here
this is Wolverine as a company and it's
just called Wolverine pre so as I
mentioned the ingredients I said in the
previous pre-workout this one has five
grams of citrulline which is a good
amount of based on the research a nice
3.2 grams of beta alanine the betin
anhydrous is good they've also got some
taurine and also elefthera root Siberian
ginseng which is it's generally
considered an adapted gin it's not a
stimulant but many find they can help to
delay fatigue so it doesn't work the
same way as a stimulant it doesn't
typically interfere with sleep but the
aluthera route here Siberian ginseng
coupled with taurine these are two
ingredients that can help with a sort of
like mental acuity Focus and attenuating
fatigue as opposed to getting really
wired and stimulated so we really like
that approach of throwing in an
adaptogen uh instead of a stimulant
which can have again similar effects we
don't interfere with sleep so silverine
pre if you're kind of over caffeine in
your pre-workouts this is our favorite
non-stem pre-workout for bodybuilding
now I know I'm really flowing a lot of
information at you in this video we have
my God so many supplements in this video
so if you want to get a written version
of this article so you can just kind of
go through it at your own pace or jump
around to what's most important to you
we have a written version for you for
that purpose so just go to Google and
write in buybin best supplements for
bodybuilding and it's going to be the
number one result and you can just go
there and click everything around all
right next up we're gonna have the best
fat burner supplement for bodybuilding
uh for us it's huge supplements
eliminate which we really like a word on
fat burners now if you guys compete then
you know what I'm talking about here
your calories are what's important here
right fat burners perhaps more than for
any other demographic they can be the
most useful for bodybuilders because
bodybuilders are getting their calories
really really closely dialed in the
average person will see a fat burner and
say great I'll take it and lose some fat
and it doesn't work like that unless
you're really closely following your
Macros and your calories and your
relatively low in body fat already
that's the bodybuilder so these sorts of
supplements they can help to induce a
little bit of extra thermogenesis and
burn a few extra calories off which can
be very meaningful especially as
competition day approaches and like you
just cannot eat less than let's say 1500
calories without feeling terrible but
you're supposed to be on 1200 something
like that or 1300 something like this
they can help to ex to burn an extra
potentially next to like one or two
maybe maybe 300 calories I encourage you
to check out the research on the
ingredients in this because they really
are well dosed and well researched they
don't have as much research support them
as like creatine or like as the fact
that protein helps to build muscle but
there are some compelling studies out
there on some of the ingredients here
like the most popular ones the most
popular ones you find in fat burning
products we're talking about Green Tea
Extract and uh red chili pepper extract
these have been seen to have like might
be significant benefits when it comes to
thermogenesis so burning more calories
than you would otherwise have also fat
oxidation like coaxing the body to burn
more fat for fuel than carbohydrates and
that it would have if you hadn't taken a
supplement and also a little bit
appetite suppression they're not quite
as well known for the appetite
suppression but nonetheless the way that
fat burners work is it's generally in
one or more of the three categories of
thermogenesis fat oxidation and appetite
suppression and the ingredients here
they heavily lean on the thermogenesis
and the fat oxidation so other
ingredients would include the grains of
paradise extract which some researchers
found that when you get the extract out
of the grains of paradise and use that
it can help to like mobilize Brown fat
tissue and also potentially help us to
burn more calories than whatever
otherwise again that's thermogenesis
there are other ingredients here as well
I don't want to sit here all day because
as you can see we have a whole lot of
ingredients here but eliminate does do a
good job at adequately dosing the
ingredients and including the most
recent ingredients when it comes to fat
burners it's not a silver bullet you do
the rest of the work but if you're a
bodybuilder you're doing the rest of the
work and you're probably the most likely
to find a product this can have some
benefit next up we have the best whey
protein for bodybuilders is this one
right here from Wolverine this is the
way isolate right what we like about
this well it's way isolate so if you're
not so aware of this kind of stuff
there are three kinds of whey out there
it's where concentrate is the least
expensive one and it has the most carbs
and fat you can process away a lot of
the carbs and fat with the way isolate
then there's hydrolyzed whey which has
some enzymes added to it to basically
make it partially pre-digested it
absorbs faster but no no way that's
really especially practical unless
you're like an Olympic level athlete
working out twice a day you know what I
mean also highlights waste is very
expensive it doesn't taste very good way
isolate is the best protein powder for
bodybuilders in our opinion what's cool
about this is for one the process per
calorie is very very very high so you
can it's just 110 calories per scoop it
is 26 grams of protein just half a gram
of fat and one gram of carbohydrate some
of the flavors might have an extra gram
of sugar depending on which one you get
this one's honey cinnamon peanut butter
which we're really big fans of but in
addition to the protein density because
like you typically especially as prep
approaches you don't want to have
extraneous carbs or fat or no more than
you want it to this is pretty much this
protein dense as a chicken breast tastes
better though the other reason we
selected this brand is is because they
include digestive enzymes so you have
protease and papine in there so it's 10
milligrams of digestive enzymes and yeah
there have been some research suggesting
that you absorb more protein and it also
absorbs faster when there are digestive
enzymes added into it right so that's
that's why we added to this one I think
especially as the system gets more
stressed this competition day approaches
stuff like that with the enzymes can be
more helpful but also just to anyone
anywhere it can be helpful it could take
away protein to digestive enzymes
naturally talk to your doctor in case
your sensitivities and stuff but the
research is pretty promising that regard
and those are all the reasons why we
think Sovereign is the best whey protein
powder for bodybuilders all right next
up we're going to talk about the best
recovery supplement for bodybuilders so
this one comes from a supplement company
called caged I'm talking about re-caged
so this this is in caged this is the mid
workout products that's the wrong one
3ks re-caged is our favorite post
workout product so this is basically
protein powder right A lot of people uh
I mean you've probably got a very high
protein diet if you're trying to lose
fat for a competition uh as you may know
many people recommend that you have well
over a gram of protein per pound of body
weight if you're really on the lower end
of body fat and trying to retain as much
muscle as humanly possible so it's
always good to have a bit of extra
protein and the way that re-caged it for
some other protein powders is that I
mean it's way isolate right so it really
is very low in carbohydrates and fat
you're getting 28 grams of protein for
two grams of carbohydrates and one gram
of fat and I've added in a couple of
extra ingredients in here that could
potentially help to improve recovery
we've also got some adhesive enzymes
here to help it absorb well there's also
some glutamine in here which it might
play a role in helping to build new
muscle tissue these days most of the
research on glutamine suggests that it
could be pretty good for gut health as
well and again you know really low
calorie diets really fresh in the system
a lot your gut can usually use as much
health as it can get so the glutamine
enzymes could be good for that and then
there's some creatine and beta in
anhydrous which as I mentioned those are
common ingredients in pre-workouts but
they actually a lot of people don't know
this you don't need to take them
pre-workout you probably know about
creatine but you don't actually need to
take that pre-workout you connect them
any time of day so the idea with this is
after you finish at the gym you're going
to take some protein and it'll have some
extra ingredients in there that might
help your gut and might help your
performance the next time you're at the
gym so in this way the protein there
helps you to recover your muscles and
then the other ingredients helps you
give you a little bit extra in the tank
the next time you go to the gym favorite
post workout supplement for bodybuilders
is cage re-caged multivitamins are
another curious aspect here uh probably
as soon as they were released onto the
market I'm sure bodybuilds were the
first ones to start taking multivitamins
typically like historically bodybuilds
will take a lot of extra B vitamins
throughout the day in any case our
favorite multivitamin for bodybuilders
is this huge supplement it's called a
huge multi does it have plenty of B
vitamins yes indeed it does a whole
Suite of them but but also I got plenty
of other nutrients here that have links
to like increased performance and
increased recovery as well so in
particular I want to talk about like
this vitamin D here which you may know
has pretty strong links to uh sleep and
Bone strength and also testosterone
production plenty of zinc as well which
has like similar benefits and then
they're antioxidants which may
potentially help with like recovery and
inflammation so vitamin C is Nancy
oxygen and there's plenty of that in
here as well but in addition to that
they've got some alpha lipoic acid which
is also a cells of antioxidants and it's
also got plenty of Ginger extract here
as well which is like a pretty powerful
anti-inflammatory that a lot of people
take be it for like managing arthritis
or just to generally reduce inflammation
so again close to competition today
getting pretty beat up so a lot of
people like as much inflammation help as
they can get lastly I mean there's a lot
on here that I haven't gone through but
there are some phytonutrients on here
that you don't normally see a
multivitamins because they're not
technically vitamins or minerals but you
probably heard of lycopene before right
which is a pretty powerful nutrient for
overall health and it is found in like
tomatoes and watermelons and the fruits
and veggies that are red you're like
them in here you get lutein which is
good for the eyes and even some CoQ10
which gets a lot of attention as a means
for improving heart health so we just
really like the huge multi for just
about anyone but yeah especially if
you're like working out a lot you get a
competition coming up even if you don't
have a competition coming up this can
help to fill any gaps in your diet that
might be there next up sleep aids
moisturizing your body the more it can
be home to have some help going to sleep
and we got a really nice product here
from transparent Labs called sleep aid
as it were now transparent Labs is it's
a pretty cool supplement company they
are very transparent with all the
ingredients not just what's in it but
the precise amounts and if you go to
like the product page and the website
they'll have links to studies that
justify why they included every
ingredient and that the amount that is
in there so we really like it sleep aid
naturally it has the Melatonin which is
like a hormone that's naturally produced
in the brain that helps you to sleep and
like use track of the internal clock
when it's time to sleep but I'm
alternating production can very easily
get disrupted by artificial lights which
we are around every single day of our
lives right so melatonin can be really
helpful as a as a sleep supplement
there's just three milligrams in this
and that's also spread over three
capsules so what's nice is that it's
about the capsules that it's easy to
measure out exactly how much of these
ingredients you want right in addition
to that you've got some touch Cherry
powder which also can potentially assist
in melatonin production there's some
glycine which among other effects has
like pretty interesting reports about
like helping to make your dreams nicer
like there's worth Googling the stories
about that glycines must be pretty great
for Sleep there's also some l-theanine
as well which can help to sort of even
you out and uh sort of calm the mind a
bit typically a lot of people take
thinine with caffeine because it has a
great reputation for easing the
jitteriness that sometimes accompanies a
big hit of caffeine like help you to
focus more if you say start your day at
the office with a bunch of caffeine you
take some cleaning and you're going to
be more useful and productive but that
also means though is it just generally
helps to calm the brain a little bit if
there's a lot going on so all these
ingredients are the reason why we like
transparent Labs sleep aid as the best
sleep supplement for bodybuilders let's
do another sleep aid uh because
certainly when calories are getting low
our approach is getting crazy high
there's a lot of extra cardio you'd
think all that exercise would make it
easy to sleep but it can really stress
the system sometimes we think the best
melatonin free sleep set for
bodybuilders is one from nested Naturals
called Luna there's no shortage of folks
who try to avoid melatonin right now it
for me it's my favorite way to get to
sleep if I'm taking yourself what that
is not everyone's melatonin this is a
solid sleep aid uh what it's got here
instead is Valerian extract which is a
very well known sedative is a bit of a
strong word but there's a significant
research that suggests that uh it can
decrease time to sleep and decrease the
frequency of waking up throughout the
night and potentially make it easy to go
back to sleep when you do wake up during
the night like to go to the bathroom or
something there's also other ingredients
with similar benefits attached to them
so we're talking about passion flower
hops extract some lemon balm extract
some chamomile extract from your
favorite nighttime tea and also some
theanine which as I mentioned earlier
although some people considered a
stimulant it's actually more about
mellowing out the brain whether it's in
the face of stimulus or on your way to
sleep so we like this one design
friendly which is nice I recommend this
one if you're not crazy at melatonin but
you still want a sleep aid because this
is a bit of a less dramatic effect than
melatonin can have on folks and it's
also been third party tested for banned
substances and stuff like that so you
can be confident that you're not gonna
accidentally test positive for anything
that you show all right so we have
talked about plenty of free workouts
that contain better alanine but if you
just want beta only which I would
totally understand like if you're sick
of caffeine or you don't want to mess
around beta in anhydrous or other weird
extracts to find their way into
pre-workouts beta alanine I mean after
caffeine and creatine probably the
supplement that gets the most attention
in the realm of ergogenic AIDS like
sports performance so if you want to
just use bitter alanine
the best bit of ironing supplement is
from Wolverine free we are big fans of
it it is soy free vegan non-GMO gluten
free and that's it it's everything else
free it's just better alanine one scoop
it's five grams here five thousand
milligrams there's no flavoring there's
no sweetness some people might be
disappointed that doesn't have any
flavoring in it uh but uh plenty of
other folks especially when bodybuilding
especially when getting close to
competition day they have like a very
strict list of the things that allow
themselves to consume and things they
want like I know planning that just
won't even have Stevia or any natural
flavoring right so this is just better
onion so you can decide what to do with
it Chuck it in a shake with everything
else that you normally have put it in
some water whatever the main things note
better alanine I can't remember if I
mentioned this earlier it does produce
usually a tingling sensation on the skin
which not everybody likes it is
completely harmless and it's very
temporary uh but yeah if that wigs you
out when you get pre-workouts you're not
going to want to get straight fit on the
dosage according to your most research
uh 1.6 grams seems fine three grams
seems like a better minimum there's this
is a 5 grams group and obviously you can
just judge how much of the scoop you
want to fill up or how many scoops you
want to have but it looks like free
grams is the right amount to have but
feel you feel very free to have more
than that and if you want to get some
bit outing work in this nice simple
stripped down product without any Frills
is the best bit I'll need for body
builders next up on the list is creatine
if you're a fan of creatine you don't
want to get it inside a pre-workout or
inside a purse workout this year it's
your best bet for basic stripped down
creatine some huge supplements the
product is called creatine guess why
it's just creating something else in
there there are plenty of brands that
again they will flavor their creatine or
they'll mix it into another product but
uh I think more than anyone and more
than any other individual workout
ingredients like citrulline and alanine
I feel like most people take the
creatine as is partly that's because it
is flavorless it's completely unflavored
so it's not even that typical to dry
scoop and just have a sip of water I've
done that myself not everybody has
creatine as they approach competition
day like some people feel it makes them
bloated other people feel that it's just
like the perfect traffic supplement to
make your muscles seem like a bigger and
more defined so it's obviously it's up
to you you already know if you want
creation or not but if you're shopping
for some yeah huge supplements is the
best creatine just because it's just
like regular straight uh Nerf rails and
it's also made in the USA in a good
manufacturing practices facility so you
know it's not coming from here weird if
they are out of creating by the way if
the company runs out of creatine it is
very very popular they also creating
pills which truthfully is my favorite
way to take creatine because then I can
just put it in the my morning pills with
other my vitamins my Lexapro and all the
other stuff and just take it all at once
not to think about it so I prefer pills
myself but the creatine here as a powder
also great anyway huge supplements
that's the best place to get creatine if
you are a bodybuilder we made it to the
end everybody we got the last product
here for you and that product is the
best essential aminer bodybuilders
talking about supplements with amino
acids in them and the best one for you
is transparent Labs again this one here
is BCAA and glutamine and it's true that
BCAAs aren't as popular as they used to
be for this in the broader Community but
certainly among bodybuilders that
typically having to take whatever Health
they can get and there is some evidence
that getting this extra loose in here
and the other branched amino acids uh
can can increase the odds of like
retaining as much muscle as possible so
this is our favorite amino acid
supplement for a couple reasons for one
the serving size is big is eight grams
of branched amino acids that's two to
one to one ratio of leucine to
isoleucine and Valium so if you're after
amino acids like yeah there's very
little arguing with that ratio and with
that dosage another thing that's cool
about it is it's very unlikely you're a
vegan bodybuilder but just in case you
are these are vegan PCA games a little
known fact is that the majority of BCAAs
on the market uh they're made from like
feathers and hair this is fermented so
it's it's vegan friendly as well or if
you just generally find other BCAAs to
be not super palatable this fermented
BCAAs they've added in some extra
glutamine and also some coconut water
powder here as well just to round it out
in addition to 1500 of the recommended
intake of vitamin C so that's a big part
of why we like it uh you are probably
aware that bodybuilders will frequently
take much more than the recommended
daily minimum of nutrients just because
of the extraordinary stresses they're
putting that system under and the
extraordinary gains and benefits and
form they want their body to take right
so this gives you an extra 1600 of the
daily vitamin C and because vitamin C is
an antioxidant there's evidence to
suggest that it can have like
anti-inflammatory properties and help a
little bit with recovery right obviously
there's a lot more to it than that and
you're going to eat a lot of vegetables
but uh the extra help from the vitamin C
the extra help from the branched amino
acids I'll lot of people are content and
they feel like a bit more secure in
their like fat loss plan when they have
a product like this so this is a big
dose of branched amino acids they are
vegan friendly I guess extra vitamin C
there to help with recovery and there
are no artificial flavors or sweeteners
but they're probably listed first
because a lot of folks they'd cut out
all artificial flavors and sweeteners
just on the very slight chance they
might potentially negatively affect
something and that's especially unusual
for a BCAA supplement because BCAAs they
tend to not taste pretty good if you've
ever had them on their own they're very
very bitter and usually you need like a
lot of artificial flavors and sweetness
to make them palatable but transparent
Labs has figured out a way to do so uh
naturally without having any sucralose
or aspartame or acid sulfame potassium
or the artificial sweeteners so that's
all the reasons why we think it's a
pretty impressive product and the best
essential amino supplement bodybuilders
is BCAA and glutamine from transparent
Labs all right well that does it for our
video on
the best supplements the body build is
just remember that uh you know a lot
about your own nutrition there's a lot
of normally like caveats I would put out
here like just make sure your calories
and macros are unchecked before you
start thinking about supplements that's
what I would do for a lot of videos for
this one you guys already know what
you're doing but I do need to emphasize
I hope that you have a good China a good
nutrition coach and a bubble I hope you
have a doctor that you're able to speak
to to get some advice before you Embark
upon any new competitions or just any
new supplements in general uh all these
supplements give a wide array of effects
some people can tolerate some
ingredients better than others so again
know thyself uh get samples when you can
and see what works best for you and your
goals you already know all this stuff
anyway look good luck on competition day
man if you want to see the full written
version of this article uh you can
Google it right in Bob end best
supplements for bodybuilding it'll come
right up message me on this entire video
thanks for watching and I'll catch you
in the next one
foreign
[Music]